inetvideo.com 2017-05-31

# Privacy Policy

* * *

We at iNetVideo take the visitor’s privacy and the security of his/her personal information very seriously. Our goal is to maintain the visitor’s trust and confidence when handling his/ her personal information. What Personal Information iNetVideo collects, why is it collected, how it is protected, the circumstances under which it may be disclosed, and how it may be changed or corrected. By visiting iNetVideo and all of its affiliated websites (as defined in Terms and Conditions), the visitor consents to the subsequent practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

1\. Collecting our Visitor’s Personal Information  
2\. Use of Personal Information  
3\. When and with whom we share our Visitor’s Personal Information  
4\. Protecting the Visitor’s Information  
5\. Automatic Collection of Information: Cookies and IP Addresses  
6\. Changing and Modifying Visitor’s Account  
7\. Changes to the iNetVideo Privacy Policy  
8\. Our Policies Regarding Children  
9\. Links to Other Sites  
10\. Effective Date  
11\. Contact Us

**1\. Collection of Personal Information** [ back to top ]

We collect personal information that the visitor chooses to provide voluntarily when using any of the iNetVideo websites. This information includes his/her email address and a password when he/she registers to create his/her iNetVideo account. We do not collect personal information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. iNetVideo may also ask for personal information when the visitor contacts us about past purchases. This will allow us to protect the visitor’s confidentiality by verifying his/her identity. iNetVideo does not knowingly collect personal information about children. If a minor would like to purchase online at iNetVideo, he/she should have the assistance of a parent or guardian.

a) Purchase information

When the visitor makes a purchase using a credit card, iNetVideo collect his/her name, his/her billing address for the card, the card type, number and expiration date. iNetVideo collects this information in order to bill the visitor for his/her purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship the visitor’s order. This includes his/her email address and the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s).

b) Contacting iNetVideo.com

We will use the visitor’s email address or physical address to respond to his/her questions, suggestions, and/or requests for assistance in using any of iNetVideo’s websites

c) Other times we may collect personal information  
**  
** From time to time, iNetVideo may conduct surveys or networking efforts via our websites, email or other media. If the visitor chooses to participate, we may request his/her name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. iNetVideo will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

d) Email subscriptions

**  
**  
iNetVideo may also use the visitor’s email address to send him/her periodic bulletins or newsletters to which he/she has subscribed.

**2\. Use of Personal Information** [ back to top ]

Information we collect on iNetVideo may be used in the following ways

\- Delivering the merchandise that the visitor purchased online    
\- Registering the visitor as a member of an iNetVideo website  
\- Billing the visitor’s credit card for his/her purchases  
\- Confirming the visitor’s shopping orders  
\- Responding to the visitor’s customer service inquiries or requests  
\- Customizing the visitor’s shopping experience  
\- Stocking the products the visitor requested  
\- Sending the visitor various information like a list of releases, promotions, featured items and bulletins that he/she has chosen to receive.

**3\. When and with whom we share our Visitor’s Personal Information** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo never sells or rents visitor’s personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives and trusted service providers and contractors for the limited purposes of fulfilling the visitor’s orders; offering certain products and services in connection with our website; communicating to customers; providing customer service acknowledgement; enhancing and improving the customer shopping experience; providing a personalized shopping experience and completing credit card transactions.

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share our visitor’s personal information with any other third parties unless we have his/her express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**4\. Protecting Your Information** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo’s websites are 100% secure; we use an industry-grade 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption protocol. We are also Hacker Safe certified. These are the best online security providers. iNetVideo gives the visitor the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

\- Primary Personal Data (such as Name and Contact details)   
\- Identifiers (such as Credit Card details)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss.  
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitor’s personal data.

iNetVideo is approved by [The Royal Bank of Canada](http://www.royalbank.ca/) to process our visitors credit cards directly, by doing this, your credit information is never re-transmitted over the internet, assuring that the information you enter on our site, is processed locally and **never** goes beyond this site.

Ultimately, our visitor’s personal information is protected by the password he/she created when he/she created an account at iNetVideo (or another password he/she chose after changing a previous password). The visitor must keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Representative or any other representative of iNetVideo will ever ask the visitor for his/her password. The confidentiality of the visitor’s password is his/her responsibility to protect. He/she may change it anytime.

iNetVideo ensures that the visitor’s personal data will not be disclosed to Provincial or State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**5\. Automatic Collection of Information; Cookies and IP Addresses** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo uses a feature of the visitor’s web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identity to his/her computer. Cookies are files that the web browsers place on computer’s hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide features such as welcoming the visitor by his name, saving his/her  Wish List, storing items in his/her Shopping Cart between visits, and setting up other preferences the visitor establishes during each visit to the website.

iNetVideo also uses cookies to help determine whether the visitor came to the website from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve usernames used on the website and provide information on past purchases. This is done for convenience and saves the visitor the trouble of re-entering information on every visit to the website. Cookies cannot be used by iNetVideo to retrieve any personal information about the visitor unless he/she has previously purchased from or registered with the iNetVideo website. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about the visitor from his/her computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by him/her.

Every computer on the Internet is identified by a unique number called an IP address. If the visitor has a static IP address, he/she gets the same number each time she connects to the Internet. If the visitor has a dynamic IP address, a number is assigned from a pool of addresses maintained by his/her ISP (Internet Service Provider) on a first-come basis. iNetVideo only uses the visitor’s IP address to help diagnose problems with its server, to administer its Site, and to gather basic demographic information.

**6\. Changing and Modifying Your Account** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo gives the visitor choices and control over the collection and use of his/her Personal Information. He/she can update his/her Personal Information or remove his/her email address from iNetVideo’s email list.

There are known methods that spammers can use to hide their identity by using other people's email address to send out emails. If the visitor has any question about the genuineness of an email he/she received that appears to be from iNetVideo, contact us at support@inetvideo.com and do not furnish any kind of personal information in response to that email until you receive a response from us.

The visitor can also choose to receive email communications such as iNetVideo’s list of releases, promotions, featured items and bulletins and other forms of communication. At any time, the visitor can change his mind and cancel these FREE subscriptions. If the visitor chooses not to sign up for that email service, iNetVideo will send the visitor only emails that relate to a specific purchase or in response to an email inquiry.

**7\. Changes to the iNetVideo Privacy Policy** [ back to top ]  
This Privacy Policy was posted on our websites on 01/06/07. iNetVideo reserves itself the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will post notice of the changes on this website for thirty (30) days in advance. If the visitor does not agree to this Privacy Policy, he must immediately discontinue using this website.

**8\. Our Policies Regarding Children** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo does not sell products to be purchased by children; however, we do sell children's products which can be purchased by adults. If the visitor is under 18 years of age, he/she should immediately discontinue using this website and must not submit any information. A minor may only use the iNetVideo websites with the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

**9\. Links to Other Sites** [ back to top ]

iNetVideo provides links to affiliated entities and on occasion to other sites we think the visitor may enjoy. These sites operate independently of iNetVideo and have established their own Terms and Conditions & Privacy and Security policies. For the best online experience, iNetVideo encourages the visitor to review these Terms and Conditions & Privacy and Security policies before submitting any Personal Information through these sites.

**10\. Effective Date** [ back to top ]

The iNetVideo Privacy Policy is effective as of June 1st 2007. This Privacy Policy represents the entire understanding relating to the use of the website and prevails over any prior or contemporaneous, conflicting or additional, communications

**11\. Contact Us** [ back to top ]

For comments or inquiries about our Privacy Policy please contact us at  
By email: support@inetvideo.com  
By telephone: Toll-free at 1-866-333-3553
